Alright people, this is DJ Hurry Ken coming at you for Fuuto Hit & Groove!
Coming up next is what a lot of people are calling the hottest new song on the airwaves.
Sung by a pair of high school girls, it's Queen and Elizabeth's "Love Wars."
saikyou koishiteru itsudatte kimi dake yeah yeah
Strongest, in love, all the time, only you, yeah, yeah!
Love is strong... girls go on!
Love is strong, Yeah Yeah
kachi ni kodawaritain jyanai
I'm not trying to be competitive
uwasa no aitsu mitai ni
Unlike that certain someone
ichido heart nusumaretara
But once my heart is stolen
Get started koi no Memory Break
I get started on love's Memory Break
saikyou koishiteru itsudatte kimi dake yeah yeah
Strongest, in love, all the time, only you, yeah, yeah!
kanari yuuki dashite "HELLO"
I work up my courage to come by and say "Hello"
kocchi kara shikakeru wa
I'll make the first move
doshita nano hannou zero
I'm not sure why I get zero reaction
Can not believe koi no memory
Can't believe these memories of love
gekiatsu Boy
You're an intense boy
nyuushu shitai Your number
I want to get your number
kono machi wa mainichi Battlefield
This city's a battlefield every day
te ni iretai no wa Love so sweet
And once you get ahold of it, love's so sweet
donna kakoku na tatakai ni nattemo Let's go Girls!
No matter how harsh the fight might be, let's go girls!
kimi datte kimeta no Boyfriend
I've decided you're gonna be my boyfriend
itsuka wa yuugure Hold my hand
And one day we're going to hold hands by the sunset
koi no tame nara zettai ni taorenai
I'll never fall if it's for the sake of love
kiken na Love Wars
In these deadly Love Wars
saikyou koishiteru itsudatte kimi dake yeah yeah
Strongest, in love, all the time, only you, yeah, yeah!
Love is strong... girls go on!
Love is strong, Yeah Yeah
itsuka Scoop saretemitai
I find out someone's scooped me
uwasa no aitsu mitai ni
Maybe it's that certain someone
futari heart atsusugite
Our hearts get too hot
Get started koi no toshi densetsu
So we get started on this romantic urban legend
tegowai Boy
You're a rough boy
akirameru toka? Oh No!
Think I'll give up? Oh no!
koi shitara doko demo battlefield
When you're in love, anywhere can be a battlefield
hi no ko ga tobichiru West to East
The sparks are flying West to East
neratta target nigashitari shinai wa Let's go girls!
I never miss my target, let's go girls!
kimi dake ga risou no Boyfriend
It turns out you're the ideal boyfriend
shiawase morenaku present
A present that will mean happiness
koi no tame nara special doryoku suru
I'll make special effort for the sake of love
tobikome Love Wars
Diving into Love Wars
daisuki Boy
"I love you, boy"
sore ga ienakute
I can't bring myself to say it
setsunai Girls
These lonely girls
tatakai tsuzuketeku
Will keep fighting on
kono machi wa mainichi battlefield
This city's a battlefield every day
te ni iretai no wa Love so sweet
And once you get ahold of it love's so sweet
donna kakoku na tatakai ni nattemo Let's go Girls!
No matter how harsh the fight might be, let's go girls!
kimi datte kimeta no Boyfriend
I've decided you're gonna be my boyfriend
itsuka wa yuugure Hold my hand
And one day we're going to hold hands by the sunset
koi no tame nara zettai ni taorenai
I'll never fall if it's for the sake of love
koi no tame nara special doryoku suru
I'll make a special effort for the sake of love
tobikome Love Wars
Diving into Love Wars
saikyou koishiteru itsudatte kimi dake yeah yeah
Strongest, in love, all the time, only you, yeah, yeah!
Love is strong... girls go on!
Love is strong, Yeah Yeah